What kind of platform is this where you
do an INS certification of
₹200? After doing a certification of ₹200,
you get a link to most of the companies on the portal. There is
no such service for insurance. If you see any agent in your village, who does any individual
urgent work, sir, he has to
give a paper of this, through which
he gets the right to get insurance from one company. Even
if he makes two-three IDs from his family, then the
option left with him is to get
insurance from two-three companies, there is
no multiple, but CSC is
giving you so many plus points, it is
giving such a good platform where you do a
certification of ₹200, there is no exam,
we provide full support and help
in getting the certification done, if you do that then
your insurance service gets
activated and the
biggest plus point of insurance is that it does not have to be sold,
it is a mandatory product
in the market, whatever bike is running on the road, be it a
car, truck, bus, any  The
insurance of any type of vehicle is
mandatory, if he does not get it done by God, then
in today's time its running cost is
very high, it is on very low side, so the
customer will not get anything done, but he has to
attest to third party insurance to travel on the road, sir, so that is why
CSC is giving you such a good
service, it is giving you the option of multiple companies for
insurance,
so this is your biggest plus point
that you utilize it, on a single platform
you have the
option of all the other companies, now first of all
I want to tell you
why you have to do insurance with Isober,
sir, why do you have to do it with us only, you can do it
in Isis later,
sir, first of all we are a big brand, sir,
I will tell you in detail about all the comprehensive full insurance in the market, in whatever
insurance we do, we mostly
provide service, sir, that is the
biggest plus point, cashless
service book means that if tomorrow there is a
claim on my car, then I will park the
car in the garage and whatever
claim for it is one lakh  Whatever the claim of ₹2 lakh,
we make the entire payment directly to the garage, sir. So,
paying directly to the garage
means that the customer does not have to bear any direct dent in his pocket.
We will pay him directly the amount of one or two lakh rupees.
If we do
not provide cashless service to any company, then the
customer has to pay that money himself at the initial level.
After that, he sends his bill for
reversal. From there, it is
not known whether it will be approved or rejected, so there is
a huge risk and the
biggest thing is that he has to pay the initial amount from his pocket. So, along with the
increase in access,
this is the biggest plus point. You people are
calling me, sir, it is
absolutely clear.
First of all, let me tell you about insurance. There are
two
types of insurance, sir, one is third party
insurance, which is on-debt, which we
call first party insurance. Third
party insurance means
this is mandatory insurance from the government, which means that
you can drive your vehicle on the road.
It means that you will not be in business
and if tomorrow, due to an accident caused by your vehicle,
someone gets damaged or
dies, then that will be grave
but you will not get a claim of even ₹1 for your vehicle,
so overall, you
can drive it on the road,
but this military insurance, along with this, the
other insurance is
on damage, which we call first party
insurance, first party
insurance is comprehensive
insurance, in which if your
customer's car meets with an accident, then
he can take a claim for the vehicle,
sir, it means that it is the first partition, he can
also take a claim for the vehicle and if there is any third party damage to the
third party, if someone has an
accident with the vehicle, someone has died,
some such case happens, then
all those things will be covered, so
overall, if you make our work a
very big work for the customer, this also becomes our work, you
people have opened centers like you, then making the
customers aware is also a
big responsibility of yours, there are many
customers like this  At the time of insurance,
everyone looks at the premium very carefully, sir. In today's
time, any customer will
buy a car worth 8-10 lakhs, but when the
time for claim, that is, insurance, comes, he will think that I will
pay the minimum premium so that tomorrow, that is,
I
can drive the car on the road, but the biggest loss is done by him,
sir. We have to explain to the customer that sir,
I will do your third party
insurance, which you are saying is
very cheap, but if you have bought a
car worth 8-10 lakhs and tomorrow you meet with an
accident, there is any loss, be it
of four-five lakhs or more, even
one lakh,
you will have to spend all the money from your pocket. The
insurance company does
not pay any claim, there is no third party in third party,
sir. So, the first thing that the customer has to do is
that when your worth is this much,
you have invested 8-10 lakh rupees for buying a car, or you have
invested 50-60 thousand rupees for buying a bike, sir,
so in third party, where you  If you are paying a premium of ₹5000
then two thousand, two and a half thousand, three
thousand will seem so much but at least the
value of your vehicle will be insured. If
tomorrow there is any accident with the vehicle or
any problem occurs then a
claim will be made for it and if you look at the specific amount then
you are taking such a huge amount at
risk. In today's time no
one has money because
that vehicle treatment is done to
cover any such damage, so it is
our biggest duty. Now, regarding on-
damage, there is the ICC Lombard
portal, sir,
I told you about this, there are
two types of parameters regarding motor insurance, on-
damage and third party. Claim is not available in third party,
customer can take claim in first party. Sir, now I will
tell you about our portal, sir,
our portal, please search as many times as you want
ICC Lombard on CSC's
digital service portal, sir, there the
direct website of ICICI Lombard opens,
you will also get my number there,
sir, all the details are available.  The most plus
point is the ICS number.
ICC group of ICICI Lambadi is such a
company which invests a lot in technology too.
When the first ATM came to India, it was
brought by ICC Bank. Overall we
invest a lot and this is our part
I Partner Portal which
is a portal for our agent, an
option has been created so that he does not make any mistake,
he is friendly for him, if he is
doing something for the first time, he should understand it. So
our portal is Van Pager Portal, in
it sir, as soon as you enter the number of any bike or vehicle,
like you
enter the number of a bike or vehicle, if you go to RTO, all the
details are automatically displayed there, the
customer does not have to fill in anything in it
sir,
if I take an example of a bike policy, then
our ICC Lambert policy is
made within 1 minute. The second best part of ours is
that we
want to take a continuous 3 year policy in the long term.
For the continuous period,
we also send that 3 year policy once, sir.
Thirdly, if the old policy of any vehicle is
expired and is breaking, photo  So
you are for us, being an agent sir,
you also have a customer like CSC, you can take a
photo of the vehicle yourself, the customer can do it,
you can take a photo of the customer at his place, so what is the
biggest plus point that
photography is required in the old vehicle policy that expires,
so for photography, Banda is
also sent by us from the company, but
what is the biggest cost in it, like
in school, I think I am in Kaithal district,
today the insurance
planning is kept at your center and right now
if I display it to any of my agents
there, he will take at least two and a half hours to
follow up, but the
biggest plus point for you is that we have
given you an app, by using Il Care,
you can do the infection yourself from there and
can do the policy simultaneously, as soon as you take a
photo of the customer's vehicle, the status comes in 5 to 10 minutes,
if it is OK,
you can do the policy yourself, you do not
need to wait for anyone,
if you want to increase our customer base  If you want to increase your business, sir, then
if you do this third party policy for someone for
a year, then that customer will never
come back to you, sir, because you want to
save him from his behavior, you want to
take any service from you, sir, but if you
explain to the customer, like I will apply it
in the case of a bike, if
my bike is five years old, the OT premium in it is Rs.
349, then you can apply it, sir, that if
he is paying Rs. 800 in third party, then
his full insurance is, I have
given my example, he gets full
insurance for a 7 year old bike for Rs. 1136, which
means he has to pay Rs. 300 extra,
along with paying Rs. 300 extra, explain to
your customer that if your bike gets
stolen tomorrow or there is an accident, then
you will get the claim for it, sir, and Rs. 300
extra is being charged, at least the
damage to your bike is being covered, sir, so the
more you will bring the customer from third party to first
party, the
customer is  The more your
base will come, the better your insurance will become, sir. So, this is the
biggest plus point, sir. The
rest of our Sir
[Music]
I will take care, there is also an app on the Play Store,
sir, which you can download.
I was telling you about the brake inspection, I will take care,
you
can do the inspection yourself through the app, sir. Okay, let me
show you the portal once again. The
front of our portal, sir,
I will show you that.
This is the front of our portal, sir. This is
someone else's ID, like a login,
sir. Here your customer agent's name appears,
like Hardeep is written here. Below that,
my name is written Manish Sharma.
Below that, the mobile number appears.
You can see it, sir. You are seeing
my screen visually.
If you look at the right side, at the top, it is
written Two Wheeler, Two
Wheeler, Third Party. This is the two wheeler on the left.
This means that if you want to do full party
insurance, then
tick Two Wheeler. If you want to do third party insurance, then
tick on the right side. Similarly, the SIM card
's PCB means passenger, which we
call taxi.  Taxi vehicles are buses
which carry passengers,
JCB goods carrier vehicle, goods
carrier vehicle, sir, that is all
your smart vehicles like
truck, pick up, all the
big vehicles for washing goods
come under JCB and M/s AC,
your tractor, agriculture tractor and
JCB, whatever work you do for construction etc., comes
under miscellaneous,
now I will tell you the first example,
sir, if we have to insure someone in two wheeler, then we have to
click on two wheeler and put the gate, sir, if we have to do the
portal, then
I put the number here
and after getting the RTO,
all the details
related to the bike will be automatically picked up by the portal, the customer,
you the agent, do
not need to fill anything, like its
registration date, its RTO, like
Jaipur is written, sir, its
manufacturer is Hero Motor Corp and
its model is Hero Duet, it is automatically
picked up in the hotel, you always have to check the model,
many times those mistakes are made by someone else  You can also take it,
check once if there is any other
model you can change it, if it is
correct then you have to keep it continuous,
below this the value of your vehicle is given,
if you want to increase or decrease it then
you can also reduce its value, it is so
friendly that it can
move automatically, with this you have to increase or decrease the value,
now reducing the value means
that
you have to reduce the premium for the customer, if he does
not have any problem with the premium then you
can give it in higher side values, like in this case
my
3468 is A, if a customer wants to take personal
accident cover then he has to enter the already personal
accident cover, sir here
how many years, like on this automatically his 5
years are given and below if the customer has
previous policies details in his POS, his policy
is continuing and
you have to enter the start date of the previous year's policy here, so for
last year
like I entered the start date of my policy as
30  If in the previous policy of November 2000, suppose
his MCB was working for
50% of the time, you selected 50%
MCB and he closed the gate,
as soon as you close the gate, your premium will be
calculated and its premium will be 1490,
sir, after adding all these things, it will be covered
sir, including personal accident,
its entire cover will be covered and its
value will be 608, you just have to enter it,
sir, here you have to enter the name and address
below, name and address and email ID
mobile number and as soon as you click generate
proposal below, your policy will be punched, sir,
so you mean that once you
start working with us, sir,
you will be able to punch the bike policy within 1 minute,
similarly it is the case with vehicles too,
you can do the same in case of vehicles too and this is what
I have told you till now about motor insurance
in today's time, sir, ever since this
Corona 2019 hit after Covid-19
Sir, there is a huge demand for health insurance,
sir, and if you look at the health insurance, the hospital costing for a hospital cost
Rs. 18,000 to 20,000, so
somewhere or the other, the demand for health is huge and that
demand is huge in other areas too, sir, so
you can also sell health insurance to the customers, we have a
model of Health Mart,
we have a plan called Health Arogya Sanjivani,
here on the
CSC portal, this plan is a
policy made by IRD and it
is basically a policy designed for India,
sir, if you want to buy this policy from somewhere else or directly from
my company with these features, or from
someone else, then
its premium will be on the higher side,
but this policy has been
designed in such a way that it is easy for the
customer to buy it, and this
means that if we take its premium, suppose
I am paying Rs. 10,000 for the family,
if you want to take any other plan similar to this, then
its
premium will be much lower.  It will increase by 20-30%,
so it is a bit economical
policy somewhere but it has all the features, it
is a policy of all the companies but
ICICI stopped you from taking it.
Why should you take Sanjeevani policy, sir, like the
motor issues, I told you first of all that
in motor insurance, ICC
World provides cashless in comprehensive policy, it is the
best, in health policy
also, the customer who has
taken the policy, suppose he got dengue
and he had to be admitted in a hospital in Kaithal,
if he is admitted for 10 days in Kaithal hospital
and whatever his bill is,
sir, the customer does
not have to pay for it to the hospital, first of all we pay
directly to our hospital, right now there are
hospitals in our time, the
customer does
not have to spend any money from his pocket, the
nominal charges are those which he has to
pay, the rest of the
payment is made directly by the company to the
hospital, this is the biggest plus point, you will have to
take the help of ISIS Hambard if you look at my competition  There are
many companies in the market
which may send this plan even
cheaper, but when it comes to claim,
there will be a problem, sir. There will be
deduction in the claim. Sometimes they will say
send the bill to our Central and Mumbai or Pune,
but in ICC World, your customer was
discharged and his payment was made directly, the
customer's work was over. There is no head,
sir. I had
told you about inspection. This app has
a kind of branch, sir.
You will get every detail in it. If you have
taken any policy, you can also see that there.
You can download it.
If you have taken any health policy,
in this health policy, two consultants are
free with the doctor. Sir, as it was done during the
time of Corona, many
people hesitate to go to the hospital.
And even in today's time, if someone has a small
problem and he is thinking that if I will go to consult a
doctor for a thousand times for a hundred rupees, then with
this help policy,
you can do two free health consultations
with the doctor, sir. And this
app is quite hi-tech, it is a highly
integrity app.  Yes sir, in this it means just like
your smart watch scans your face, it also keeps
all your updates and
we have brought one more unique feature in this app sir,
if you look at your face through face scan then it will
tell everything about you,
what is your blood pressure, what is your current stress
level, so it brings a very unique
feature, so you can use this also,
you can explore more about Ikon Lombard,
our hospital, this tyre and all
our facilities, you will get them all in it
sir, my name is Manish Sharma,
please note down my number, my number
is 98166
10893, that is why I am giving you my number in the group chat
also,
I am giving this 98166 10893, if anyone has any
query related to this then please you can ask, you will have to go there only
or
can go to any garage, I will tell the customer sir,
whenever any customer gets a
claim, whenever he gets a claim, he has
our  The toll free number is
1800,
you have to register your claim on it, our
survey will guide you, go to this garage and
park your vehicle,
all the work will be done there automatically, you are
talking about cashless, it is the same, isn't it sir, it gets
registered automatically, all the work
starts automatically, your server and we
contact you directly,
just once the customer registers the claim,
I have shared my number with me, if you
ever need any support, I will
help you completely
9816610893
Hello, sir, tell me, will you
get it in the one you mentioned or will you have to get it
separately, we have a
certification for it, sir, it
comes after refreisan, its certification is done there,
₹200 is charged for you, as soon as
your certification is done, there are some
questions in it
like you cannot get its certificate,
like I cleared the insurance test etc. in CSC, will I get it in that
or will I have to do it again, no, no,
if you have done the insurance test in CSC  If you
clear it,
all your services will be activated in it. When did you
clear the service test?
[Music] It is
not showing activated in it because of my
service, whereas I have got the certificate. There is no
problem. You can
WhatsApp me on 121 your name and CSC
ID in whose name you have the CSC ID. I will
check once
98166.
[Music]
Yes sir,
how are you?
Plus point, as I told you,
we also do short term policies. We do
not have any competition in the market who does short
term policies, sir. So, that is a plus
point for us, sir. So, what is there in this,
if you want to do short term policy for someone, sir, for a
bike, sir, whatever third party
short term policy there is, sir, that is your
comprehensive policy. You will have to do it for a third party
van year. If you
buy a bike like Splendor in normal way and want to do
it short term, then the
policy is made for ₹2.50 per month
and this is the biggest plus point for
those who want to buy a car.
And if you pitch this product, sir,
you have no competition for short term. All the
agents in the market  You
cannot do a short term policy, any
agent of the respected company, any dealer sitting there,
cannot do a short term policy and this
isolambard only specific one does
short term policy on the CSC portal,
this is the point sir, you can call me on 121
sir, after the call I will do it for you on Android,
okay sir, the
short term insurance in insurance
which is your normal insurance,
in motor insurance which we also do
and if the company does a one year
policy, if you want to do it for
2 months or 3 months, you
can do that policy, yes sir, yes sir, so
this is our biggest plus point,
so please market it a little,
yours also
sir, if for the first time you will do a short term policy
and in the previous policy its
MCB is 50%, then you can give 50%,
but if you are doing a continuous short term
policy, then you will
not get its MCB, when fit, the benefit
of NCB which is closed,
still your policy is for 365 days  should be  You
can take it for the first time, you cannot take it for the second time,
but in most cases, you will do it for short term only
where there is breaking of the policy
etc., so this is a plus point,
I will tell you the NCB details,
sir, for the first time I
bought a car in 2020, so if
I do not take any claim till 2021, then I will get
20% make in the policy of 21, similarly
I will continue to get 25% next year, in the third year
also, from fourth to 45 and in the fifth year, the
maximum slab for me is 50%, so
I bought a car in 2020 and
I took the claim for that car in 22, so the
25% benefit that I was supposed to get became
zero, whenever whichever question takes the claim, that
NCB will become zero, it will
start from zero again, sir and note down the
MCB close of
your
range of the old policy, yes
NCB remains, sir, the old means the
period of NCB, if  Spoon,
today my policy
will expire and if I take the policy after 4 months then
I will not get the benefit of MV, the
maximum slab for that is,
he will have to continue the policy within 90 days, only
then he will get the benefit of NCB,
hello
sir, please check once, I put it on my screen, the
screen was showing it to you, it should open
on customer.
Hello Sir
and his brother had an accident in 2-4 months and
he took a claim, there is a
time period of one month, even then he
can make a claim or he can make a one time
[music]
ok Sir, thank you, I have
talked to you in great detail Sir and
when we have such meetings, listen when
we have such meetings, Sir please
try to understand a little bit,
if I am telling you something for doing
business here, but the thing which is
closed from the company's side is the Two Wheeler On
Damage Policy, I told you my talk in great detail and
I told you that
our portal is not working and the
most popular one will be live from a certain date, okay, so
if that policy is
absolutely Sir, I said this to you because of this
and I explained it to you in detail,
right now please all of you, whoever you are,
please listen carefully, what I
understand is that in today's time, Sir, if someone buys a bike,
then the government policy is that its
five year policy will be
made by the dealer only, from where you have
purchased the bike, I have
In 2022, on 22nd November, he purchased a Karizma bike.
His policy from 22nd to 23rd of the next year is for full years
and the policy from 23rd
till 12th will be for third party.
Okay, now every year he has to
purchase the full policy separately.
His previous
policy was from Reliance company. Next time he
wants to take it from LMBA or HDFC. He can
take any kind of policy. Now
what are the plus and minus points in it? For example, the
policy which was to be
renewed on 28th in the next year i.e. in 2023,
instead of 28th November, he delayed it by 6 days till 4th December
and got his policy done.
Sir, his policy will continue, Sir,
but the extra money of one year which was from the
third party, friend, Rs. 2000, has been paid
till 27th. The question is, the payment of third party has been
made for 5 years, there will be a gap in it
because when he gets his last year's policy
renewed, Sir, then his policy will be done.  The third
party policy will expire on November 28th,
but its own damage
policy will expire on December 4th. So, no
company will pay the premium for the last year's policy, it will have to be paid in
full. So, in
order to save two days, you have directly imposed a dent of ₹1200 on the customer.
This is what I was trying to tell you.
Today, you have put a hold on the customer and
in a couple of days, his car met with a
bike accident. Sir, he will first
come to you and say that you had said that you will get it done,
now you get it done, sir. Neither will
we pay for the company nor will you pay. So, do
n't sit in the market taking such risks, this will
spoil your reputation. First of all, take
third party insurance for example, if there was
any problem in it,
in the case of two-wheelers, ISOCELL does
not do inspection, sir. You
can take full insurance whenever you
feel that the company will not pay the old claim,
sir, whenever you
register a claim, it gets known that if there was an
old claim and you have just taken the
policy.  If you have got it done then it shows the
daily survey details in it but after today if
your bike meets with any accident or
any issue occurs then all that is
covered in it but in case of a vehicle which
is expired from the old policy then there are
photos in it. Thirdly our PCB
segment is autos which are small autos
and these are pick ups, Tata S,
even in these we do not inspect,
in case of breaking we do insurance without photos,
this is also your plus
point because a customer came to you and
you immediately issued him insurance,
this is also a plus point, so you
can put a little promotion on this also.
Hello Sir
again
[Music]
will clarify the point a little again,
okay Sir, I was telling you that nowadays all the
new bikes that are launched have a
five year policy, Sir, the
dealer gives the policy for 5 years, so
what happens in it is that for the first year it is
its full policy and for the next 4 years it is
its third part, okay, suppose
he has bought the bike in between till 25  He has taken insurance for
BC 21, the one who is 21 to 25 years old is
his third party, now for 20-21 years it
is already assured, when he will have to get insurance every year in 21, from
21 to 22, from 22 to 23 to 24 to
25, if his new year is
every year, in this the member gets a
removable spoon in the middle, the one for
22 which is the third year, he
delayed it by four days and in getting the new year
policy,
when his last year policy was to expire on 1st November 2025, it got
delayed by four days, so
he will have to pay all the money, he will have to
pay the TP money
and the full amount as well,
otherwise he would have had to pay only the Udi-Udi money, so
somewhere the customer has
lost ₹8, ₹900 whatever TP charges he has paid.  We can get some
kind of PDF file so that
we can explain everything clearly to the customer so that there is
no problem later. Can we get some
document like the one you told sir, we sir
document sir, this insurance, actually as soon as
you
start working, your understanding of it will
increase, the concept of insurance
remains the same, friend, I was changing it,
no document is made in it like this,
but you do it from time to time, if
you ever need support, you can
call me, it is not a Saturday, if
I will not take the variable then I will refer my team
ahead, they will contact you,
but you will never face any problem,
you start working once, whoever works,
we provide them WhatsApp from time to time, if there is
any gifting, we also provide that, so all these
things are
your plus, but the most important thing is that you have to keep
interacting with the customer, if
you ever start working so much,
your
queries will automatically start increasing
because you  You will learn half the things from the customer, some of them
might be yours, how it happens, then you will
learn automatically, a
customer came to me on the 24th on the 23rd, it was getting
finished on the 24th,
I talked to you brother, please get it done,
you also helped me with the online portal
and in that you said our portal
of your wheeler is not working for the last 15 days and
I cannot tell whether it will start or not in the next 15-20 days,
hence you should get it done from another company,
right now it will cost more with another company,
Sir Naresh ji, I mean whatever you are doing, you are doing it
great, you should understand my point, I have
explained it very well, you have to
value every emotion of the customer, right now
he is saying, Sir, it is possible that with your
loved one,
he was making a deal of ₹700, take it,
and if the company is charging ₹900 from him,
taking ₹200 extra, you are not understanding,
but you have given a gap of 5-6 days for it, due to which
you have calculated it.  Sir, you have caused a loss of ₹800
to the customer. Tomorrow the same customer will come to you
when his last call will be that
you have caused a loss to him and
in 5 days he has a claim and some
accident happens, then who will survive. Sir, am I
wrong? Sir, my business is to do
business here, but whatever you do
for us, only then our business will increase.
But I will mislead you. Today I will
reduce my business, Sir, I will not incur loss tomorrow
for that. I am
sitting here for the long term and will give you the
best suggestion and will guide you the best. Sir, if
someone knows the business, it will not be considered bad. The
customer has suffered a
loss of one year by not updating you. Sir, please consider this,
even if it is a loss of one day, it is equal to that and this is the loss
of the month. Sir, this is what I am
explaining to you. Sir, will you listen to me for a minute?
Sir, Sir, I bought a new bike 2 years ago, it
expired a year ago, the
company had repaired it,
you are telling me what I will do with it.  If it is from the
first party then it will be done
sir, yes it will be done,
call me whenever you need support,
okay then it is okay, for
any other query from anyone else, sir
you have my number reachable,
whenever you feel like it, please call me sir.